从一个Activity移动到另一个Activity
To move from one activity. In this case,
这里就是从我们的Sunshine的MainActivity
the MainActivity in our sunshine app, to another, here
移动到DetailActivity，这个过程叫startActivity()。但是注意当我们
the DetailActivity, we call StartActivity. But note that when
使用startActivity()这个方法时，并不是直接传递这个Activity的
using the StartActivity method, rather than specifying the class
类名称来开始，而是把类名称
name of the activity to start directly, that
包装在一个Intent里。
class name is packaged explicitly within an intent. The
这个基本前提是很简单的。不管什么时候你需要让你的
basic premise is simple. Whenever you need your app
应用程序组件进行互相交流，或者与系统交流，
components to communicate with each other, or the system,
应该用Intent来指定目标
you use intents to identify the
你的APP中启动Activity是
target destination. Starting activities within your
最简单的例子。
app is the simplest example. [SOUND]
通过使用Context和Activity的类名称
With your intent explicitly indicating the target
能明确地指定Intent的目标。这种直接使用目标组件
using the context and a class name of the activity. Intents that use the
名字的Intent，也被称作明确的Intent
name of the component you're targeting directly, are known as explicit intents.